<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<odoo>
    <template id="sa_fsma_scheme_usa">
        <div id="portal_fsma_content" t-attf-class="#{'card pb-5' if not print else ''}">
            <div id="introduction" class="#{'pb-2 pt-3 card-header' if not print else ''}" style="text-align: center;">
                    <h3><b>PRIMUS AUDITING OPERATIONS AUDIT<br/>SERVICES AGREEMENT</b></h3>
            </div>
            <div class="card-body">
                <p>
                    Please sign and return this Services Agreement (“Agreement”) within 24 hours of receipt. JS Audit Group, Inc., 
                    dba Primus Auditing Operations (“Primus Auditing Ops”) is not responsible for changes to estimated costs or any 
                    additional costs incurred when Service Agreements are returned late. All estimates are calculated in U.S. dollars.
                </p>
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-12">
                        <p style="text-align:left;"><b>Organization Name (“Customer”): </b><span t-field="serviceagreement.organization_name"/></p>
                    </div>
                </div>
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-12">
                        <p style="text-align:left;"><b>Billing Customer: </b><span t-field="serviceagreement.customer_name"/></p>
                    </div>
                </div>
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-6">
                        <p style="text-align:left;"><b>RFC #: </b><span t-field="serviceagreement.customer_vat"/></p>
                    </div>
                    <div class="col-6">
                        <p style="text-align:left;"><b>Registration Number: </b><span t-field="serviceagreement.name"/></p>
                    </div>
                </div>
                
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-12">
                        <p style="text-align:left;"><b>Billed in: </b><span>United States</span></p>
                    </div>
                </div>
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-6">
                        <p style="text-align:left;"><b>Contract E-mail: </b><span t-field="serviceagreement.contract_email"/></p>
                    </div>
                    <div class="col-6">
                        <p style="text-align:left;"><b>Phone #: </b><span t-field="serviceagreement.phone"/></p>
                    </div>
                </div>
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-6">
                        <p style="text-align:left;"><b>Invoice E-mail: </b><span t-field="serviceagreement.invoice_email"/></p>
                    </div>
                    <div class="col-6">
                        <p style="text-align:left;"><b>Tentative Date: </b><span t-field="serviceagreement.start_date"/> - <span t-field="serviceagreement.end_date"/></p>
                    </div>
                </div>
                
                <br/>
                <table class="table">
                    <thead class="thead-dark" style="text-align:center">
                        <tr>
                        <th scope="col">Services</th>
                        <th scope="col">Quantity</th>
                        <th scope="col">Audit Fee</th>
                        </tr>
                    </thead>
                    <tbody>
                        <t t-set="current_subtotal" t-value="0"/>
                        <tr t-foreach="serviceagreement.services_ids" t-as="service">
                            <t t-set="current_subtotal" t-value="current_subtotal + service.price_subtotal"/>
                            <td><span t-field="service.name"/></td>
                            <td style="text-align:right;"><span t-field="service.product_uom_qty"/></td>
                            <td style="text-align:right;"> <span t-field="service.price_subtotal"/></td>
                        </tr>
                        <tr>
                            <th style="text-align:right;" colspan="2" esc="row">Total Services:</th>
                            <th style="text-align:right;" colspan="1" scope="row">
                                <strong class="mr16">
                                    <span t-esc="current_subtotal" t-options="{'widget': 'monetary', 'display_currency': serviceagreement.sign_sa_agreements_id.sale_order_id.currency_id}"/>
                                </strong>
                            </th>
                        </tr>
                    </tbody>
                </table>
                <div style="page-break-after: always;">
                </div>
                <div style="text-align: center;">
                    <h4>
                        <b><em>Services to be delivered by Primus Auditing Operations</em></b>
                    </h4>
                </div>
                <p>
                    Estimated Travel Expenses: - Travel expenses are estimated and are subject to 
                    change based on actual travel expenses incurred.
                </p>
                <p>
                    Travel expenses are on a direct reimbursement basis and include all expenses for 
                    transportation, accommodation and meals. Whenever possible trips are combined with 
                    other business and expenses are divided to reduce the total cost for all of our customers.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <b>1. DELIVERY.</b> Note that audit reports are sent electronically via email. 
                    Hardcopies are available.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <b>2. IDEMNIFICATION &amp; HOLD HARMLESS.</b> Customer acknowledges and agrees it shall indemnify, 
                    defend and hold Primus Auditing Ops harmless from all claims, demands, losses, liabilities, 
                    costs, expenses, obligations and damages of every kind and nature, known and unknown, including 
                    reasonable legal fees associated with Customer's commodity and operations, irrespective of the 
                    cause or nature of the liability.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <b>3. LIMITATION OF LIABILITY.</b> Customer hereby releases Primus Auditing Ops and its respective 
                    affiliates including but not limited to employees, officers, directors, shareholders, from any loss 
                    or liability suffered by Customer, as defined below, resulting from services performed under this 
                    Agreement. Such release shall include any actual, incidental, consequential or other damages beyond 
                    amounts paid to Primus Auditing Ops for auditing performed and/or facilitated by Primus Auditing Ops. 
                    Customer further acknowledges and agrees that Primus Auditing Ops' liability is limited only to audit 
                    work performed by it, and the parties expressly acknowledge that Primus Auditing Ops is not liable for 
                    Customer's commodity, its safety, or quality.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <b>4. GOVERNING LAW / VENUE.</b> This Agreement shall be governed by and construed in accordance with 
                    the laws of the State of California. In the event that it is necessary to institute any action to 
                    enforce any right granted herein or to redress any alleged breach hereof, then the exclusive venue for 
                    such action shall reside with the applicable Superior or Municipal Court located in Santa Maria, California.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <b>5. GOVERNING AGENCY COMPLIANCE.</b> 
                    Customer expressly acknowledges that Primus Auditing Ops and its auditors are not a governing agency, and does 
                    not set the industry standards for safety or protocol. Customer also acknowledges that Primus Auditing Ops. 
                    provides results of audits and makes no representation or warranty regarding the quality of the Customer's products, 
                    facility, fields, methods, or other audited subjects. The client acknowledges and agrees that Primus Auditing Ops 
                    is not a representative of the United Stated Food and Drug Administration (FDA), nor is it a representative of any 
                    other federal, state, or local governmental agency. As such, Primus Auditing Ops does not have the authority to make 
                    representation or warranties on behalf of any governmental agency. The client is solely responsible for compliance 
                    with all applicable laws and regulations related to the products or services provided by Primus Auditing Ops.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <b>6. RIGHT TO REFERRAL.</b> 
                    Customer acknowledges that Primus Auditing Ops is, or may, contract out the auditing services performed for Customer. 
                    Because an independent auditor is engaged in his/her own independent contracting business and is not an employee of 
                    Primus Auditing Ops, Primus Auditing Ops will not obtain insurance (professional liability, workers' compensation, 
                    general liability, auto, etc.) for the auditor or his/her employees. Independent auditors agree by a separate referral 
                    agreement to obtain his/her own insurance coverage and furnish a copy of the certificate of insurance to 
                    Primus Auditing Ops. Furthermore, in those instances in which an independent auditor is retained, Primus Auditing Ops 
                    will be acting in the sole capacity of independent contractor and any information or data received will be merely 
                    transmitted between parties, making no independent judgment, representations or warranties as to the facts, 
                    observations or inferences made relative to the same.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <b>7. TERM AND TERMINATION.</b> This Agreement, and its terms, shall continue in effect until such time as it is 
                    terminated by Customer or Primus Auditing Ops, as provided for below. Representations, warranties, and any 
                    corresponding obligations thereto, made in the course of this Agreement shall continue beyond termination.
                    <ul>
                        <li><b>Termination for Cause.</b> If either party fails to fulfill any term or condition of this Agreement, 
                        such failure shall constitute a breach of this Agreement by that party. In such a circumstance, 
                        the non-breaching party shall provide, by regular mail, written notice to the breaching party and include a 
                        sufficient description of the relevant conduct in violation of this Agreement. The breaching party shall 
                        have 15 days from the date the notice is mailed to cure the breach and come into compliance with the terms 
                        of this Agreement. If, after 15 days, the breaching party has not cured the breach, the non-breaching party 
                        may immediately terminate this Agreement with no further obligations by providing written notice of 
                        termination.</li>
                        <li><b>Voluntary Termination.</b> Either party may voluntarily terminate this Agreement upon fifteen days' 
                        written notice to the other party. If this Agreement is terminated by Customer, any ongoing assessments 
                        made by Primus Auditing Ops shall immediately be considered void and of no effect.</li>
                        <li><b>Termination by Customer After Desktop Review Portion of Audit.</b> If Customer voluntarily terminates 
                        this Agreement in accordance with Section 8.b. above, but after Primus Auditing Ops has begun the desktop 
                        review portion of the audit, Customer acknowledges and agrees that it shall be responsible for, and, upon 
                        termination, shall immediately pay to Primus Auditing Ops, an amount equal to ONE-THIRD (1/3) of the Audit Fee 
                        indicated in the “Audit Fee/Total Services” box on page 1 of this Agreement. Failure on Customer's behalf to 
                        pay said amount is a material breach of this Agreement by Customer.</li>
                    </ul>
                </p>
                <p>
                    <b>8. BILLING.</b> The Customer agrees to pay Primus Auditing Ops within 30 days of billing.
                    <br/>
                </p>



               
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-6">
                        <p style="text-align:center;">
                            <b>"PRIMUS AUDITING OPS" <br/> JS Audit Group, Inc., a California corporation</b>
                        </p>
                    </div>
                    <div class="col-6">
                        <p style="text-align:center;">
                            <b>“CUSTOMER” <br/> <span t-field="serviceagreement.customer_name"/></b>
                        </p>
                    </div>  
                </div>
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-6">
                        <!-- <p style="text-align:center;">
                            <img t-attf-style="#{'max-width: 100%;' if not print else 'width:327px; heigth:327px;'}" t-att-src="image_data_uri(serviceagreement.coordinator_id.sign_signature)" t-if="serviceagreement.coordinator_id.sign_signature"/>
                        </p> -->
                        <p style="text-align:center;">
                            <img t-attf-style="#{'max-width: 100%;' if not print else 'width:327px; heigth:327px;'}" t-att-src="image_data_uri(serviceagreement.sign_sa_agreements_id.coordinator_signature)" t-if="serviceagreement.sign_sa_agreements_id.coordinator_signature"/>
                        </p>
                    </div>
                    <div class="col-6">
                        <p style="text-align:center;">
                            <img class="img img-responsive" style="width:327px; heigth:327px;" t-att-src="image_data_uri(serviceagreement.sign_sa_agreements_id.signature)" t-if="serviceagreement.sign_sa_agreements_id.signature"/>
                        </p>
                    </div>  
                </div>
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-6">
                        <p style="text-align:left;">
                            <b>By: </b>Operations Specialist
                        </p>
                    </div>
                    <div class="col-6">
                        <p style="text-align:left;">
                            <b>By: </b><span t-field="serviceagreement.sign_sa_agreements_id.position"/>
                        </p>
                    </div>   
                </div>
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-6">
                        <!-- <p style="text-align:left;">
                            <b>Date: </b><span t-field="serviceagreement.sign_sa_agreements_id.document_date"/>
                        </p> -->
                        <p style="text-align:left;">
                            <b>Date: </b> <span t-field="serviceagreement.sign_sa_agreements_id.coordinator_signature_date" t-if="serviceagreement.sign_sa_agreements_id.coordinator_signature_date" widget="date"/>
                        </p>
                    </div>
                    <div class="col-6">
                        <p style="text-align:left;">
                           <b>Date: </b><span t-field="serviceagreement.sign_sa_agreements_id.signature_date" t-if="serviceagreement.sign_sa_agreements_id.signature_date"/>
                        </p>
                    </div>  
                </div>
                <div style="text-align: center;" t-if="print == False">
                    <hr class="mt-0 mb-1" style="border-top: 1px solid"/>
                    <ul class="list-inline" style="text-align: center;">
                        <li class="list-inline-item">Primus Auditing Ops Confidential Document</li>
                        <li class="list-inline-item">Cert075</li>
                        <li class="list-inline-item">Rev.1 10/02/2023</li>
                    </ul>
                </div>
                
            </div>
        </div>
    </template>
</odoo>