<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<odoo>
    <template id="sa_pgfs_scheme_usa">
        <div id="portal_sa_pfgs_usa_content" t-attf-class="#{'card pb-5' if not print else ''}">
            <div id="introduction" class="#{'pb-2 pt-3 card-header' if not print else ''}" style="text-align: center;">
                    <h3><b>PRIMUS AUDITING OPERATIONS<br/>PRIMUSGFS SERVICES AGREEMENT</b></h3>
            </div>
            <div class="card-body">
                <p>
                    Please sign and return this services agreement within 24 hours of receipt. JS Audit Group, Inc., dba 
                    Primus Auditing Operations (“Primus Auditing Ops”) is not responsible for changes to estimated costs 
                    or any additional costs incurred when Service Agreements are returned late. All estimates are calculated 
                    in U.S. dollars.
                    
                </p>
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-12">
                        <p style="text-align:left;"><b>Organization Name (“Customer”): </b>
                        <span t-field="serviceagreement.organization_name"/></p>
                    </div>
                </div>
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-12">
                        <p style="text-align:left;"><b>Billing Customer: </b>
                        <span t-field="serviceagreement.customer_name"/></p>
                    </div>
                </div>
                <br/>
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-6">
                    <p style="text-align:left;"><b>RFC #: </b><span t-field="serviceagreement.customer_vat"/></p></div>
                    <div class="col-6">
                    <p style="text-align:left;"><b>Registration  Number: </b><span t-field="serviceagreement.name"/></p></div>
                </div>
                <br/>
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-6">
                    <p style="text-align:left;"><b>Billed In: </b>United States</p></div>
                    <div class="col-6">
                    <p style="text-align:left;"><b>Version: </b><span t-field="serviceagreement.version"/></p></div>
                    
                </div>

                <br/>
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-6">
                    <p style="text-align:left;max-width:400px;"><b>Contact E-mail: </b><span t-field="serviceagreement.contract_email"/></p></div>
                    <div class="col-6">
                    <p style="text-align:left;max-width:400px;"><b>Phone #: </b><span t-field="serviceagreement.phone"/></p></div>
                    
                </div>

                <br/>
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-6">
                    <p style="text-align:left;max-width:400px;"><b>Invoice E-mail: </b><span t-field="serviceagreement.invoice_email"/></p></div>
                
                <div class="col-6"  t-if="serviceagreement.sign_sa_agreements_id.sale_order_id.audit_type != 'unannounced'">
                    <p style="text-align:left;max-width:400px;"><b>Tentative Date: </b><span t-field="serviceagreement.start_date"/> - <span t-field="serviceagreement.end_date"/></p></div>  
                </div>

                <br/>
                
                <table class="table" style="font-family: 'Times New Roman'; font-size: 16px; color: black;">
                    <thead  style="text-align:center">
                        <tr>
                            <th scope="col">Services</th>
                            <th scope="col">Quantity</th>
                            <th scope="col">Audit Fee</th>
                        </tr>
                    </thead>
                    <tbody>
                        <t t-set="current_subtotal" t-value="0"/>
                        <tr t-foreach="serviceagreement.services_ids" t-as="service">
                            <t t-set="current_subtotal" t-value="current_subtotal + service.price_subtotal"/>
                            <td><span t-field="service.name"/></td>
                            <td style="text-align:right;"><span t-field="service.product_uom_qty"/></td>
                            <td style="text-align:right;"> <span t-field="service.price_subtotal"/></td>
                        </tr>
                        <tr>
                            <th style="text-align:right;" colspan="2" esc="row">Total Services:</th>
                            <th style="text-align:right;" colspan="1" scope="row">
                                <strong class="mr16">
                                    <span t-esc="current_subtotal" t-options="{'widget': 'monetary', 'display_currency': serviceagreement.sign_sa_agreements_id.sale_order_id.currency_id}"/>
                                </strong>
                            </th>
                        </tr>
                    </tbody>
                </table>
                <div style="page-break-after: always;">
                </div>
                <div style="text-align: center;">
                    <h4 style="text-align:center">
                        <b><em>Services to be delivered by Primus Auditing Operations</em></b>
                    </h4>
                </div>
                <h4 class="text-center">THIS IS NOT AN INVOICE</h4>
                <p>
                    Estimated Travel Expenses: - Travel expenses are estimated and are subject to change based on actual travel expenses incurred.
                </p>
                <p>
                    Travel expenses are on a direct reimbursement basis and include all expenses for transportation, accommodation and meals. 
                    Whenever possible trips are combined with other business and expenses are divided to reduce the total cost for all of our customers.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <b>1. DELIVERY.</b> Note that audit reports and certificates are sent electronically 
                    via email. Hardcopies are available.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <b>2. DATA OWNERSHIP.</b> All data submitted by Primus Auditing Ops into the PrimusGFS 
                    certification system operated by the scheme owner, becomes the property of Azzule Systems 
                    for use in preparing specific statistical comparisons, and generic use in reports, 
                    presentations and other materials.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <b>3. LIMITATION OF LIABILITY.</b> Customer hereby releases Primus Auditing Ops and Primus 
                    Group Inc. and their respective affiliates, from any loss or liability suffered by Customer, 
                    as defined below, resulting from services performed under this Agreement. Such release shall 
                    include any actual, incidental, consequential or other damages beyond amounts paid to Primus 
                    Auditing Ops for auditing performed and/or facilitated by Primus Auditing Ops. Customer 
                    further acknowledges and agrees that Primus Auditing Ops' liability is limited only to 
                    audit work performed by it, and the parties expressly acknowledge that Primus Auditing 
                    Ops is not liable for Customer's commodity, its safety, or quality.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <b>4. GOVERNING LAW / VENUE.</b> This Agreement shall be governed by and construed in 
                    accordance with the laws of the State of California. In the event that it is necessary to 
                    institute any action to enforce any right granted herein or to redress any alleged breach 
                    hereof, then the exclusive venue for such action shall reside with the applicable Superior or 
                    Municipal Court located in Santa Maria, California.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <b>5. GLOBAL FOOD SAFETY INITIATIVE and PRIMUSGFS.</b> 
                    Customer expressly acknowledges that Primus Auditing Ops and its auditors are not a governing 
                    agency, and does not set the industry standards for safety or protocol. Customer also acknowledges 
                    that PrimusGFS is an audit program benchmarked and governed by the Global Food Safety Initiative's 
                    (GFSI) standards and promulgated requirements. All results posted by Primus Auditing Ops will be 
                    based on GFSI criteria. Customer expressly acknowledges that Primus Auditing Ops has not created 
                    these standards and criteria, but is only acting in accordance with GFSI.
                    <ul>
                        <li>
                            <b>CONSENT TO RELEASE INFORMATION - GFSI AND SCHEME OWNER.</b> 
                            As part of its requirements for benchmarking Audit schemes to the GFSI standard, GFSI requires 
                            that all contracting parties for GFSI benchmarked audits authorize the Certification Body to 
                            make all audit records from Customer's audit available to the Scheme Owner (Azzule) and GFSI. 
                            By executing this Agreement, Customer hereby consents to and authorizes Primus Auditing Ops to 
                            release all audit documents to the Scheme Owner and GFSI for internal use purposes. 
                        </li>
                    </ul>
                </p>
                <p>
                    <b>6. RIGHT TO REFERRAL.</b> 
                    Customer acknowledges that Primus Auditing Ops is, or may, contract out the auditing services performed for 
                    Customer. Because an independent auditor is engaged in his/her own independent contracting business and 
                    is not an employee of Primus Auditing Ops, Primus Auditing Ops will not obtain insurance (professional 
                    liability, workers' compensation, general liability, auto, etc.) for the auditor or his/her employees. 
                    Independent auditors agree by a separate referral agreement to obtain his/her own insurance coverage and 
                    furnish a copy of the certificate of insurance to Primus Auditing Ops. Furthermore, in those instances in 
                    which an independent auditor is retained, Primus Auditing Ops will be acting in the sole capacity of 
                    independent contractor and any information or data received will be merely transmitted between parties, 
                    making no independent judgment, representations or warranties as to the facts, observations or inferences 
                    made relative to same.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <b>7. AUDIT AND SURVEILLANCE.</b> 
                    Customer agrees and acknowledges free access is required to be made for scheduled audit, as well as possible 
                    random surveillance pursuant to PrimusGFS scheme requirements, of customer's operation including but not 
                    limited to: examination of documentation, records, and access to the equipment, location(s), area(s), 
                    personnel, and full physical inspection of customer's subcontractors. Customer agrees to allow observers 
                    from Primus Auditing Ops and/or varying governing bodies if customer's audit or certification is randomly 
                    selected for surveillance for quality assurance purposes. Customer further agrees to grant free access in 
                    order to verify continued compliance with certification. Customer acknowledges complaints related to compliance 
                    must be documented, and subsequent investigation of complaints is mandatory. Documentation of complaints and 
                    investigation may be subject to inspection during audit or surveillance or at the request or Primus Auditing 
                    Ops at any time. Customer acknowledges action must be taken in regards to complaints or deficiencies found in 
                    products that affect certification requirements with accompanying documentation of actions taken. Customer 
                    acknowledges that its failure to fully comply with this section, either during the time of audit or any other 
                    time during the certification period, is a material breach of this agreement and can result in Customer's 
                    certification being revoked without further notification.  Therefore, customer agrees to allow observers 
                    from Primus Auditing Ops, the Scheme Owner, and/or the Accreditation body to observe the conduct of any 
                    audit for any reason, including to monitor auditor performance.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <b>8. PRODUCT CERTIFICATION.</b> Customer shall comply with the following:
                    <ul>
                        <li>Customer agrees to always fulfill the certification requirements.</li>
                        <li>Customer shall further comply by implementing appropriate changes when 
                        they are communicated via Primus Auditing Ops to Customer.</li>
                        <li>Additionally, customer agrees if certification applies to ongoing 
                        production that the certified product continues to fulfill 
                        the product requirements.</li>
                    </ul>
                </p>
                <p>
                    Request for copies of certification documents for third parties will be provided in their entirety. 
                    Customer acknowledges it may not make claims in regards to certification that are inconsistent with 
                    the scope of the audit performed. Furthermore, the customer may not use product certification in a 
                    manner that is misleading or unauthorized, or in a manner that would damage the reputation of Primus 
                    Auditing Ops or the PrimusGFS Scheme. Additionally, customer acknowledges that if certification is 
                    suspended, terminated or revoked customer must discontinue advertising any material in reference to 
                    such certification and return certification documents.
                </p>
                <p>
                    The customer agrees to inform Primus Auditing Ops, without delay, of changes that may affect its 
                    ability to conform to the certification requirements. Examples of changes can include but are not limited to:
                    <ul>
                        <li>The legal, commercial, organizational status of ownership</li>
                        <li>Organization and management e.g. key managerial, decision making or technical staff</li>
                        <li>Modifications to the product or the production method</li>
                        <li>Contact address and production sales</li>
                        <li>Major changes to the quality management system</li>
                    </ul>
                </p> 
                <p>
                    The customer agrees to inform Primus Auditing Ops, without delay, of any significant food safety 
                    related events including recalls, outbreaks, significant regulatory food safety nonconformities, 
                    and/or food safety related prosecutions.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <b>9. UNANNOUNCED AUDITS.</b>
                    GFSI now requires that auditees undergo an unannounced audit on a periodic basis.  Customer hereby 
                    represents that it acknowledges, understands, and agrees that, in conformance with GFSI requirements, 
                    and the PrimusGFS General Regulations, Customer is required to, and will cooperate with the unannounced 
                    audit requirement as described in the PrimusGFS General Regulations.  If Customer has selected, or is 
                    selected by Primus Auditing Ops, to undergo an unannounced audit, it acknowledges that it must be in 
                    production and able to accommodate the Customer's audit(s) on any dates not declared as blackout dates. 
                    Failure by Customer to allow the auditor on site to perform the audit, or otherwise fail to accommodate 
                    the certification process will result in cancellation of the audit and Customer will be billed, and 
                    acknowledges it will be liable to Primus Auditing Ops for, a fee in an amount equal to ONE-THIRD (1/3) 
                    of the Audit Fee indicated in the “Audit Fee/Total Services” box on page 1 of the Agreement.   
                </p>
                <p>
                    <b>10. COMPLIANCE AND MARKS OF CONFORMITY, ADDENDUM “A”.</b>  
                    The customer must comply with any requirements that may be prescribed in the certification scheme relating 
                    to the use of marks of conformity, and on information related to the audit. Additionally, in making reference 
                    to the certification in communication media such as documents, brochures, or other advertising as may be 
                    permitted, Customer must comply will all Primus Auditing Ops requirements and certification scheme requirements 
                    for use of Primus Auditing Ops' and the certification scheme's names, marks, and logos. The parties expressly 
                    agree that the attached Addendum “A”, and all provisions listed therein are hereby incorporated as an addendum 
                    to this Primus Auditing Operations PrimusGFS Service Agreement.
                </p>
                <p>
                    A violation of the use of the PrimusGFS trademark, as outlined herein and the attached Addendum A shall constitute 
                    a breach of this Agreement by customer.    In the event that Customer, its employees, or officers, improperly use 
                    the trademark and logo of PrimusGFS without the consent of Primus Auditing Ops or the scheme owner, Customer shall 
                    have fifteen (15) calendar days, following written notice from Primus Auditing Ops or the Scheme Owner of the improper 
                    use, to cure the improper use. If Customer fails to cure the improper use, this Agreement is voidable by Primus Auditing 
                    Ops, and Customer's certification, and the documents associated therewith, will be immediately revoked.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <b>11. TERM AND TERMINATION,</b>
                    <br/>
                    <ul>
                        <li><u><b>Termination for Cause</b></u> This Service Agreement and the sublicense for use of the PrimusGFS trademark 
                        granted herein shall be indefinite, ending at the time of expiration of Customer's Certification. If either party fails 
                        to fulfill any term or condition of this Agreement, such failure shall be considered a breach of this Agreement. 
                        The breaching party shall have 10 calendar days from the time of receipt of written notice from the other party to cure 
                        such breach. If after 10 days, the breaching party has not cured the breach, the non-breaching party may terminate this 
                        Agreement with no further obligations. The 10-day notice provision and termination is not applicable to violation of the 
                        Trademark use, as described in Section 9 herein - where the cure time upon notice will be 15 days. </li>
                        <li>
                        <u><b>Voluntary Termination.</b></u> Either party may voluntarily terminate this Agreement upon fifteen days' written notice 
                        to the other party.  If this Agreement is terminated by party, all sublicenses and certifications granted by Primus Audit Ops 
                        to Customer after such termination shall not be valid. Subject to Section 10.c. below, either party may voluntarily terminate 
                        this Agreement upon fifteen days' written notice to the other party.   If this Agreement is terminated by Customer, 
                        all sublicenses and certifications granted by Primus Auditing Ops to Customer hereunder shall not be valid past the 
                        date of Termination.
                        </li>
                        <li>
                        <b>Termination by Customer.</b> Desktop Review Portion of Audit. If Customer voluntarily terminates this Agreement in 
                        accordance with Section 10.b. above, but after Primus Auditing Ops has begun the Desktop Review portion of the Audit, Customer 
                        acknowledges and agrees that it shall be responsible for, and pay to Primus Auditing Ops, an amount equal to ONE-THIRD (1/3) of 
                        the Audit Fee indicated in the “Audit Fee/Total Services” box on page 1 of the Agreement. Failure on Customer's behalf to do so 
                        is a material breach of this Agreement by Customer.
                        </li>
                    </ul>
                </p>
                <p>
                    <b>12. PAYMENT AND CANCELLATIONS.</b> The Customer agrees to pay Primus Auditing Ops within 30 days of billing. All services 
                    rendered by the Company are provided on a non-refundable basis. Customer acknowledges that the Company will make its best effort 
                    to ensure that all invoices are correctly issued. However, should Customer note any possible errors, Customer agrees to notify our 
                    Billing Department within 10 days of the issuance of the errant invoice. After 10 days, all invoices will be assumed to be correct, 
                    and no further billing adjustments will be made.
                    <br/>
                    <br/>
                    A cancellation administration fee of $200.00 may be charged for any audit cancellation within 21 days of the scheduled audit date. 
                    This cancellation fee excludes any additional expenses related to travel and labor if incurred.
                </p>
                 <div style="page-break-after: always;">
                </div>
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-6">
                        <p class="text-start">
                            Date: <span t-field="serviceagreement.sign_sa_agreements_id.document_date" widget="date"/>
                        </p>
                    </div>
                </div>

                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-6">
                        <p style="text-align:center;">
                            <b>"PRIMUS AUDITING OPS"</b>
                        </p>
                    </div>
                    <div class="col-6">
                        <p style="text-align:center;">
                            <b>"CUSTOMER"</b>
                        </p>
                    </div>  
                </div>
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-6">
                        <p style="text-align:center;">
                            <b>JS Audit Group, Inc., a California corporation</b>
                        </p>
                    </div>
                    <div class="col-6">
                        <p style="text-align:center;">
                            <b><span t-field="serviceagreement.sign_sa_agreements_id.sale_order_id.partner_id.name"/></b>                            
                        </p>
                    </div>  
                </div>
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-6">
                        <p style="text-align:center;">
                            <img t-attf-style="#{'max-width: 100%;' if not print else 'width:327px; heigth:327px;'}" t-att-src="image_data_uri(serviceagreement.coordinator_id.sign_signature)" t-if="serviceagreement.coordinator_id.sign_signature"/>
                        </p>
                    </div>
                    <div class="col-6">
                        <p style="text-align:center;">
                            <img class="img img-responsive" style="width:327px; heigth:327px;" t-att-src="image_data_uri(serviceagreement.sign_sa_agreements_id.signature)" t-if="serviceagreement.sign_sa_agreements_id.signature"/>
                        </p>
                    </div>  
                </div>
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-6">
                        <p style="text-align:left;">
                            <b>By: </b><span t-field="serviceagreement.coordinator_id.name"/>
                        </p>
                    </div>
                    <div class="col-6">
                        <p style="text-align:left;">
                            <b>By: </b><span t-field="serviceagreement.sign_sa_agreements_id.signer_name" t-if="serviceagreement.sign_sa_agreements_id.signer_name"/>
                        </p>
                    </div>  
                </div>
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-6">
                        <p style="text-align:left;">
                            <b>Audit Coordinator</b>
                        </p>
                    </div>
                    <div class="col-6">
                        <p style="text-align:left;">
                            <b>Title: </b><span t-field="serviceagreement.sign_sa_agreements_id.position"/>
                        </p>
                    </div>  
                </div>
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-6">
                        <p style="text-align:left;">
                            <b>Date: </b> <span t-field="serviceagreement.sign_sa_agreements_id.document_date"/>
                        </p>
                    </div>
                    <div class="col-6">
                        <p style="text-align:left;">
                            <b>Date: </b><span t-field="serviceagreement.sign_sa_agreements_id.signature_date" t-if="serviceagreement.sign_sa_agreements_id.signature_date"/>
                        </p>
                    </div>  
                </div>
                <div style="page-break-after: always;">
                </div>
                <div style="text-align: center;">
                    <h4 style="text-align:center; font-weight:Bold;">Addendum A</h4>
                    <h4 style="text-align:center; font-weight:Bold;">ADDITIONAL PRIMUSGFS SUBLICENSE AND CERTIFICATION AGREEMENT ADDENDUM</h4>
                </div>
                
                <p>
                    This addendum (“Exhibit A”) is an addition to, and the terms hereby incorporated into, the Sublicense and Certification 
                    Agreement for PrimusGFS. Services Agreement (“Agreement”). 
                    <br/>
                    <br/>
                    <u><b>Marks of Conformity</b></u>
                    <br/>
                    <br/>
                    Azzule Systems. is the legal owner of the trademark “PRIMUSGFS” and the logo collectively “PRIMUSGFS”
                </p>
                <p>
                    Contracting Party is granted a non-exclusive and revocable sublicense for use of the PRIMUSGFS trademark, 
                    logo, and name on the following conditions, all of which Contracting Party acknowledges and agrees to:  
                </p>
                <p>
                    The use of the PRIMUSGFS trademark shall not appear on the product, or consumer packaging, nor shall it 
                    be used at the point of sell in direct connection to single products. 
                </p>
                <p>
                    Contracting Party may only use the PRIMUSGFS trademarks on pallets that only contain PRIMUSGFS certified produce; 
                    trademark shall not appear at point of sale in this instance. 
                </p>
                <p>
                    PRIMUSGFS certified producers may use the PRIMUSGFS trademark in business to business communication, and for 
                    traceability, segregation or identification purposes on site at the production location. 
                </p>
                <p>
                    Trademark use is granted for promotional use on print-outs, flyers, hardware and electronic displays (not directly 
                    linked to certified product) and in business-to-business communication by retailers, associate and supplier members. 
                    The trademark shall not be used on promotional items, apparel items, accessories, bags, personal care items or in 
                    connection with retail store services.
                </p>
                <p>
                    The PRIMUSGFS logo and trademark must be obtained from Primus Auditing Operations, in order to ensure conformance 
                    with exact corporate color and format, and may only be used in a manner consistent with PRIMUSGFS requirements. 
                </p>
                <p>
                    A violation of the use of the PrimusGFS trademark, as outlined herein and the attached Addendum A shall constitute a 
                    breach of this Agreement by customer.    In the event that Customer, it's employees, or officers, improperly use 
                    the trademark and logo of PrimusGFS without the consent of Primus Auditing Ops or the scheme owner, Customer shall 
                    have fifteen (15) calendar days, following written notice from Primus Auditing Ops or the Scheme Owner of the improper 
                    use, to cure the improper use. If Customer fails to cure the improper use, this Agreement is voidable by Primus Auditing 
                    Ops, and Customer's certification, and the documents associated therewith, will be immediately revoked. 
                </p>
                <p>
                    Nothing herein shall be construed to relieve the parties from their respective obligations under the agreement.
                </p>
                
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-6">
                        <p style="text-align:center;">
                            <b>"PRIMUS AUDITING OPS"</b>
                        </p>
                    </div>
                    <div class="col-6">
                        <p style="text-align:center;">
                            <b>"CUSTOMER"</b>
                        </p>
                    </div>  
                </div>
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-6">
                        <p style="text-align:center;">
                            <b>JS Audit Group, Inc., a California corporation</b>
                        </p>
                    </div>
                    <div class="col-6">
                        <p style="text-align:center;">
                            <b><span t-field="serviceagreement.sign_sa_agreements_id.sale_order_id.partner_id.name"/></b>
                        </p>
                    </div>  
                </div>
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-6">
                        
                        <p style="text-align:center;">
                            <img t-attf-style="#{'max-width: 100%;' if not print else 'width:327px; heigth:327px;'}" t-att-src="image_data_uri(serviceagreement.coordinator_id.sign_signature)" t-if="serviceagreement.coordinator_id.sign_signature"/>
                        </p>
                    </div>
                    <div class="col-6">
                        <p style="text-align:center;">
                            <img class="img img-responsive" style="width:327px; heigth:327px;" t-att-src="image_data_uri(serviceagreement.sign_sa_agreements_id.signature)" t-if="serviceagreement.sign_sa_agreements_id.signature"/>
                        </p>
                    </div>  
                </div>
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-6">
                        <p style="text-align:left;">
                            <b>By: </b><span t-field="serviceagreement.coordinator_id.name"/>
                        </p>
                    </div>
                    <div class="col-6">
                        <p style="text-align:left;">
                            <b>By: </b><span t-field="serviceagreement.sign_sa_agreements_id.signer_name" t-if="serviceagreement.sign_sa_agreements_id.signer_name"/>
                        </p>
                    </div>  
                </div>
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-6">
                        <p style="text-align:left;">
                            <b>Audit Coordinator</b>
                        </p>
                    </div>
                    <div class="col-6">
                        <p style="text-align:left;">
                            <b>Title: </b><span t-field="serviceagreement.sign_sa_agreements_id.position"/>
                        </p>
                    </div>  
                </div>
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-6">
                        <p style="text-align:left;">
                            <b>Date: </b><span t-field="serviceagreement.sign_sa_agreements_id.document_date" widget="date"/>
                        </p>
                    </div>
                    <div class="col-6">
                        <p style="text-align:left;">
                            <b>Date: </b><span t-field="serviceagreement.sign_sa_agreements_id.signature_date" t-if="serviceagreement.sign_sa_agreements_id.signature_date"/>
                        </p>
                    </div>  
                </div>
                
                <div style="text-align: center;" t-if="print == False">
                    <hr class="mt-0 mb-1" style="border-top: 1px solid"/>
                    <ul class="list-inline" style="text-align: center;">
                        <li class="list-inline-item">Primus Auditing Ops Confidential Document</li>
                        <li class="list-inline-item">PGFS-016</li>
                        <li class="list-inline-item">Rev. 12 10/02/2023</li>
                    </ul>
                </div>
                
            </div>
        </div>
    </template>
</odoo>