<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<odoo>
    <template id="sa_smeta_scheme_usa">
        <div id="portal_smeta_content" t-attf-class="#{'card pb-5' if not print else ''}">
            <div id="introduction" class="#{'pb-2 pt-3 card-header' if not print else ''}" style="text-align: center;">
                    <h3><b>PRIMUS AUDITING OPERATIONS<br/>SERVICE AGREEMENT</b></h3>
            </div>
            <div class="card-body">
                <p>
                    Please sign and return this service agreement within 24 hours of receipt. JS Audit Group, Inc., dba Primus 
                    Auditing Operations (“Primus Auditing Ops”) is not responsible for changes to estimated costs or any additional 
                    costs incurred when service agreement are returned late. All estimates are calculated in U.S. dollars.
                </p>
               

                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-6">
                        <p style="text-align:left;"><b>Organization Name: </b><span t-field="serviceagreement.organization_name"/></p>
                    </div>
                    <div class="col-6">
                        <p style="text-align:left;"><b>Billing Customer: </b><span t-field="serviceagreement.customer_name"/></p>
                    </div>
                </div>
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-6">
                        <p style="text-align:left;"><b>RFC#: </b><span t-field="serviceagreement.organization_vat"/></p>
                    </div>
                    <div class="col-6">
                        <p style="text-align:left;"><b>Registration Number: </b><span t-field="serviceagreement.name"/></p>
                    </div>
                </div>
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-6">
                        <p style="text-align:left;"><b>Billed In: </b>United States</p>
                    </div>
                    <div class="col-6">
                        <p style="text-align:left;"><b>Audit Scope: </b><span t-field="serviceagreement.audit_scope"/></p>
                    </div>
                </div>
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-6">
                        <p style="text-align:left;"><b>Contract E-mail: </b><span t-field="serviceagreement.contract_email"/></p>
                    </div>
                    <div class="col-6">
                        <p style="text-align:left;"><b>Type of Audit: </b><span t-field="serviceagreement.audit_type"/></p>
                    </div>
                </div>
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-6">
                        <p style="text-align:left;"><b>Invoice E-mail: </b><span t-field="serviceagreement.invoice_email"/></p>
                    </div>
                    <div class="col-6">
                        <p style="text-align:left;"><b>Customer Requirements: </b><span t-field="serviceagreement.client_requirements"/></p>
                    </div>
                </div>
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-6">
                        <p style="text-align:left;"><b>Phone #: </b><span t-field="serviceagreement.phone"/></p>
                    </div>
                    <div class="col-6">
                        <p style="text-align:left;"><b>Audit Length: </b><span t-field="serviceagreement.audit_duration"/></p>
                    </div>
                </div>
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-12">
                        <p style="text-align:left;"><b>Agreed Date (s): </b><span t-field="serviceagreement.start_date"/> - <span t-field="serviceagreement.end_date"/></p>
                    </div>
                </div>

                <table class="table">
                    <thead class="thead-dark" style="text-align:center">
                        <tr>
                        <th scope="col">Services</th>
                        <th scope="col">Quantity</th>
                        <th scope="col">Audit Fee</th>
                        </tr>
                    </thead>
                    <tbody>
                        <t t-set="current_subtotal" t-value="0"/>
                        <tr t-foreach="serviceagreement.services_ids" t-as="service">
                            <t t-set="current_subtotal" t-value="current_subtotal + service.price_subtotal"/>
                            <td><span t-field="service.name"/></td>
                            <td style="text-align:right;"><span t-field="service.product_uom_qty"/></td>
                            <td style="text-align:right;"> <span t-field="service.price_subtotal"/></td>
                        </tr>
                        <tr>
                            <th style="text-align:right;" colspan="2" esc="row">Total Services:</th>
                            <th style="text-align:right;" colspan="1" scope="row">
                                <strong class="mr16">
                                     <span t-esc="current_subtotal" t-options="{'widget': 'monetary', 'display_currency': serviceagreement.sign_sa_agreements_id.sale_order_id.currency_id}"/>
                                </strong>   
                            </th>
                        </tr>
                    </tbody>
                </table>
                <div style="page-break-after: always;">
                </div>
                <div style="text-align: center;">
                    <h4>
                        <b><em>Services to be delivered by Primus Auditing Operations</em></b>
                    </h4>
                    <br/>
                    <h4>
                        <b>THIS IS NOT AN INVOICE</b>
                    </h4>
                </div>
                <p>
                    Estimated Travel Expenses: - Travel expenses are estimated and are subject to change based on actual 
                    travel expenses incurred.<br/>
                    Travel expenses are on a direct reimbursement basis and include all expenses for transportation, 
                    accommodation and meals. Whenever possible, trips are combined with other business and expenses are 
                    divided to reduce the total costs for all of our customers
                </p>
                <p>
                    <b>1. DELIVERY.</b> Audit reports an information related to the audit are shared through the SEDEX Platform.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <b>2. TRANSFER OF DATA TO OUTSIDE PARTIES.</b> Primus Auditing Ops may be required to submit information 
                    obtained during the audit to either Supplier Ethical Data Exchange ("SEDEX") and/or to the Association of 
                    Professional Social Compliance Auditors (“APSCA”) for its authorized use. By executing this Agreement, Customer 
                    acknowledges that such information may be provided to the applicable SEDEX and/or APSCA, and consents to the 
                    transfer of such information.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <b>3. LIMITATION OF LIABILITY.</b> Customer hereby releases Primus Auditing Ops, its employees, directors, 
                    principals, agents, and affiliates, from any loss or liability suffered by Customer, resulting from services 
                    performed under this Agreement. Such release shall include any actual, incidental, consequential or other 
                    damages beyond amounts paid to Primus Auditing Ops for auditing performed and/or facilitated by Primus Auditing 
                    Ops. Customer further acknowledges and agrees that Primus Auditing Ops' liability is limited only to the audit 
                    work performed by it, and the parties expressly acknowledge that Primus Auditing Ops is not liable for Customer's 
                    commodity, its safety, or quality.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <b>4. GOVERNING LAW / VENUE.</b> This Agreement shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws 
                    of the State of California. In the event that it is necessary to institute any action to enforce any right granted 
                    herein or to redress any alleged breach hereof, then the exclusive venue for such action shall reside with the 
                    Superior Court located in Santa Maria, California.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <b>5. RIGHT TO REFERRAL.</b> Customer acknowledges that Primus Auditing Ops is, or may, contract out the auditing 
                    services performed for Customer. Because an independent auditor is engaged in his/her own independent contracting 
                    business and is not an employee of Primus Auditing Ops, if Primus Auditing Ops refers the audit out to a contractor, 
                    it will not obtain insurance (professional liability, workers' compensation, general liability, auto, etc.) for the 
                    auditor or his/her/its employees. Independent auditors agree by a separate referral agreement to obtain his/her own 
                    insurance coverage and furnish a copy of the certificate of insurance to Primus Auditing Ops. Furthermore, in those 
                    instances in which an independent auditor is retained, Primus Auditing Ops will be acting in the sole capacity of 
                    independent contractor and any information or data received will be merely transmitted between parties, making no 
                    independent judgment, representations or warranties as to the facts, observations or inferences made relative to same.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <b>6. AUDIT AND SURVEILLANCE.</b> Customer agrees and acknowledges free access is required to be made for any 
                    scheduled audit, as well as possible random quality assurance checks (depending on the audit scheme's requirements) 
                    of customer's operation including but not limited to: examination of documentation, records, and access to the 
                    equipment, location(s), area(s), personnel, and full physical inspection of Customer's subcontractors. Customer 
                    agrees to allow observers from Primus Auditing Ops and/or varying governing bodies if customer's audit or 
                    certification is randomly selected for surveillance for quality assurance purposes. Customer further agrees 
                    to grant free access in order to verify continued compliance with certification. Customer acknowledges complaints 
                    related to compliance must be documented, and subsequent investigation of complaints is possible, and in some cases 
                    may be mandatory. Documentation of complaints and investigation may be subject to inspection during audit or 
                    surveillance or at the request or Primus Auditing Ops at any time. Customer acknowledges that its failure to fully 
                    comply with this section, either during the time of audit or any other time during the certification period, is a 
                    material breach of this agreement and can result in Customer's certification being revoked without further notification. 
                    The Customer understands and agrees to perform Follow-up Audits when corrective actions cannot be verified in a desk 
                    review, for example, in the event of critical non-compliances.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <b>7. CUSTOMER OBLIGATIONS.</b> The Customer agrees to comply with the points cited in the SMETA audit, under the 
                    Ethical Trading Initiative Base Code (ETI), as well as the applicable local Laws. Any deviation detected during 
                    the audit will be reported and indicated during the closing meeting and in the corresponding document (CARP), for 
                    which Customer must take corrective actions to cure the deviation, and is responsible for entering them into the 
                    SEDEX platform Customer's corrective actions, as well as entering them into the SEDEX platform is the sole 
                    responsibility of the Customer, to which Customer acknowledges, understands, and agrees. 
                </p>
                <p>
                    In the event that a new on-site visit is required to verify corrective actions as determined in the closing meeting 
                    of the corresponding audit, the Customer agrees in advance to pay all costs related to said visit, namely travel 
                    expenses, mileage, auditor and administrative expenses. Primus Auditing Operations, for this purpose, will send an 
                    individual quote accordingly.
                </p>
                <p>
                    Customer further agrees:
                    <br/>
                    <ul style="list-style-type: lower-latin">
                        <li>
                            Customer must deliver the Self-Assessment Questionnaire (SAQ) at least 15 days prior to the date of the onsite 
                            visit/ audit. Likewise, you must provide the ZC and ZS registration numbers to Primus Auditing Ops at least 
                            5 days before the audit, otherwise the audit will be rescheduled and the per diem payment is subject to the 
                            assigned auditor having made any expenses prior to the audit cancellation either by the client or due to lack 
                            of registration on the Sedex platform.
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            Customer is responsible for managing all the logistics necessary to carry out the audit and evaluation by 
                            representatives of Primus Auditing Ops, which includes access to records, documentation, facilities and 
                            everything that is necessary to verify compliance with the regulations and requirements pursuant to SMETA 
                            Customer is responsible for compliance with SMETA and the guidelines of the Ethical Trade Initiative Base 
                            Code (ETI), undertakes to carry out all the activities necessary to maintain compliance after the audit, 
                            as well as the implementation of measures consistent with the continuous improvement in accordance with 
                            the conditions reflected in the Audit Report.
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            Customer agrees to inform Primus Auditing Ops of any change in the operation that may affect the Client's 
                            ability to comply with the audit requirements or that generates a significant change in the way the client 
                            performs its activities.
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            Customer agrees to apply the corrective actions within the time period agreed to during the closing meeting 
                            with the auditor. In the event that it is unable to apply or otherwise the corrective actions, it will 
                            submit the situation in writing to both Primus Auditing Ops and the auditor.
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            Customer agrees to act in good faith and inform Primus Auditing Operations in writing of any significant 
                            change that contravenes the provisions of the ETI Base Code evaluated.
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            Customer agrees to have representatives from senior management, managers responsible for key functions 
                            (for example HR and production) and trade unions / workers' representatives at the time of the onsite audit.
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            Customer agrees to give the auditor full access to the applicable audited operation, documents and personnel 
                            during the onsite visit in order to perform the SMETA audit. 
                            <ul style="list-style-type: lower-roman">
                                <li>
                                    If an auditor has Full Access Denied, the auditor shall trigger an alert in all cases. If the auditor 
                                    is able to enter the site but cannot access any of the necessary information, they shall raise an 
                                    alert and a Non-Compliance.
                                </li>
                                <li>
                                    If an auditor has Partial Access Denied, the auditor shall continue with the audit, but raise a 
                                    Non-Compliance with a detailed description of the issue(s).
                                </li>
                            </ul>
                        </li>
                    </ul>
                </p>
                <p>
                    <b>8. AUDIT RESULTS.</b> The Client must comply with the following:
                    <ul style="list-style-type: lower-latin">
                        <li>The client agrees to always comply with the requirements of the methodology.</li>
                        <li>The client shall comply by implementing the appropriate changes when communicated 
                        through Primus Auditing Ops to the client.</li>
                    </ul>
                </p>
                <p>
                    The client acknowledges that it cannot make assertions regarding the audit results that are 
                    inconsistent with the scope of the audit performed. Furthermore, the client may not use the audit 
                    results in a misleading or unauthorized manner, or in a manner that damages the reputation of Primus 
                    Auditing Ops. In addition, the client acknowledges that the times for closing non-conformities should 
                    be discussed during the closing of the audit with the auditor so that they are established in the CAPR 
                    Corrective actions report.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <b>9. CONFIDENTIALITY.</b> Primus Auditing Ops hereby represents and agrees that all information obtained 
                    or developed in connection with any audit performed under this Agreement, and for any audit performed for 
                    social compliance or otherwise governed by APSCA shall be kept confidential and shall not be disclosed to 
                    any party other than Customer, except in the following circumstances:
                    <ul style="list-style-type: lower-latin">
                        <li>
                            Customer requests and/or authorizes Primus Auditing Ops, in writing, to release such information 
                            to a specific third party; or
                        </li>
                        <li>
                           Where disclosure of such information to a third party is required in order for Primus Auditing Ops 
                           to perform and execute the services under this Agreement; or,
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            Primus Auditing Ops is required, pursuant to applicable and governing laws or regulation (by deposition, 
                            interrogatories, requests for information or documents in legal proceedings, subpoena, civil 
                            investigative demand or similar process), to disclose any or all of such obtained information; 
                            and in such case, only to the extent required by law; or, 
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            Disclosure of such obtained information is required by Primus Auditing Ops to obtain legal or ethical advice 
                            regarding compliance with applicable laws, applicable codes and/or standards. Where confidentiality is not 
                            governed by a recognized professional code of conduct, an appropriate non-disclosure agreement must be 
                            executed by the third party prior to disclosure of such information; or,
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            Disclosure is required to establish a claim or defense by Primus Auditing Ops in an adversarial proceeding.
                        </li>
                    </ul>
                </p>
                <p>
                    <b>10. TERM AND TERMINATION </b>  
                    <ul style="list-style-type: lower-latin">
                        <li>
                            <b>Termination for Cause.</b> This Service Agreement shall be indefinite, ending at the time of expiration 
                            of Customer's Certification. If either party fails to fulfill any term or condition of this Agreement, 
                            such failure shall be considered a breach of this Agreement. The breaching party shall have 10 calendar days 
                            from the time of receipt of written notice from the other party to cure such breach. If after 10 days, the 
                            breaching party has not cured the breach, the non-breaching party may terminate this Agreement with no 
                            further obligations.  The 10-day notice provision and termination is not applicable to violation of the 
                            Trademark use, as described in Section 11 herein - where the cure time upon notice will be 15 days.
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <b>Voluntary Termination.</b> Either party may voluntarily terminate this Agreement upon fifteen days' 
                            written notice to the other party.  If this Agreement is terminated by either party, all certifications 
                            granted by Primus Audit Ops to Customer after such termination shall not be valid.
                        </li>
                    </ul>
                </p>
                <p>
                    <b>11. BILLING.</b>  
                    <ul style="list-style-type: lower-latin">
                        <li>
                            <u><b>Audits performed by Mexico Office.</b></u> For all Audits scheduled with and performed by the 
                            Primus Auditing Ops office in Mexico, Customer agrees it shall pay the total audit fees prior to the 
                            scheduling and performance of the Audit. The total audit fee may include, but not limited to audit fee, 
                            admin fees, report entry times, travel time, evidence review, and travel expenses.  Primus Auditing Ops 
                            will not schedule or perform any audit under this Agreement prior to receipt of full payment for audit fees. 
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <u><b>Audits performed by US, Chile, and Costa Rica Offices.</b></u> For all Audits scheduled with and 
                            performed by Primus Auditing Ops' offices in the United States of America, Chile, or Costa Rica; Customer 
                            agrees of hall pay 50% of the total audit fees must be paid in full prior to the scheduling and performance 
                            of the Audit. The total audit fee may include, but not limited to audit fee, admin fees, report entry times, 
                            travel time, evidence review, and travel expenses.
                            <br/><br/>
                            Customer agrees to pay Primus Auditing Ops the outstanding balance within 30 days or receipt of invoice from 
                            Primus Auditing Ops remaining amount. The total audit fee might include but not limited to audit fee, admin 
                            fees, report entry times, travel time, evidence review, and travel expenses.
                        </li>
                    </ul>
                </p>
                <p>
                    <b>12. CANCELLATION FEES.</b> If Customer cancels or otherwise reschedules a scheduled audit date, it acknowledges, 
                    understands, and agrees that Customer shall be responsible for all non-refundable travel costs incurred by Primus 
                    Auditing Ops associated with that audit. In addition to any incurred travel costs, any change or cancellation of 
                    an audit by Customer that occurs within 15 business days of the scheduled audit will be charged a cancellation fee 
                    of 50% of the audit.  If, on the day of the audit, the auditor or any representative of Primus Auditing Ops is denied 
                    access to the field, facilities, or any area necessary to perform the audit, Customer understands, acknowledges, 
                    and agrees that it shall be responsible for all audit fees quoted herein, in addition to all travel costs.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <b>13. LOGO and URN.</b> The guidelines for the usage of the Sedex Member Logo can be found on their website 
                    <a target="_blank" href="https://www.sedex.com/">(www.sedex.com)</a> 
                    and in the document titled Sedex Ambassador toolkit. The Customer must not misuse the SMETA report, CAPR and/or URN.
                </p>
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-6">
                        <p class="text-start">
                            Dated: <span t-field="serviceagreement.sign_sa_agreements_id.document_date" widget="date"/>
                        </p>
                    </div>
                </div>
               
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-6">
                        <p style="text-align:center;">
                            "PRIMUS AUDITING OPS"
                        </p>
                    </div>
                    <div class="col-6">
                        <p style="text-align:center;">
                            "CUSTOMER"
                        </p>
                    </div>  
                </div>
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-6">
                        <p style="text-align:center;">
                            <b>JS Audit Group, Inc., a California corporation</b>
                        </p>
                    </div>
                    <div class="col-6">
                        <p style="text-align:center;">
                            
                        </p>
                    </div>  
                </div>
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-6">
                        <img t-attf-style="#{'max-width: 100%;' if not print else 'width:327px; heigth:327px;'}" t-att-src="image_data_uri(serviceagreement.coordinator_id.sign_signature)" t-if="serviceagreement.coordinator_id.sign_signature"/>
                    </div>
                    <div class="col-6">
                        <img class="img img-responsive" style="width:327px; heigth:327px;" t-att-src="image_data_uri(serviceagreement.sign_sa_agreements_id.signature)" t-if="serviceagreement.sign_sa_agreements_id.signature"/>
                    </div>  
                </div>
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-6">
                        <p style="text-align:left;">
                            <b>By: </b><span t-field="serviceagreement.coordinator_id.name"/>
                        </p>
                    </div>
                    <div class="col-6">
                        <p style="text-align:left;">
                            <b>By: </b><span t-field="serviceagreement.sign_sa_agreements_id.signer_name" t-if="serviceagreement.sign_sa_agreements_id.signer_name"/>
                        </p>
                    </div>  
                </div>
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-6">
                        <p style="text-align:left;">
                            <b>Audit Coordinator</b>
                        </p>
                    </div>
                    <div class="col-6">
                        <p style="text-align:left;">
                            <b><span t-field="serviceagreement.sign_sa_agreements_id.position"/></b>
                        </p>
                    </div>  
                </div>
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-6">
                        <p style="text-align:left;">
                            <b>Date: </b><span t-field="serviceagreement.sign_sa_agreements_id.document_date"/>
                        </p>
                    </div>
                    <div class="col-6">
                        <p style="text-align:left;">
                           <b>Date: </b><span t-field="serviceagreement.sign_sa_agreements_id.signature_date" t-if="serviceagreement.sign_sa_agreements_id.signature_date"/>
                        </p>
                    </div>  
                </div>

               
                <div style="text-align: center;" t-if="print == False">
                    <hr class="mt-0 mb-1" style="border-top: 1px solid"/>
                    <ul class="list-inline" style="text-align: center;">
                        <li class="list-inline-item">PrimusAuditingOps Confidential Document</li>
                        <li class="list-inline-item">SCL-011</li>
                        <li class="list-inline-item">R.5   10/02/2023</li>
                    </ul>
                </div>
                
            </div>
        </div>
    </template>
</odoo>